<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on deadchannel</title>
    <link>https://deadchannel.xyz/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on deadchannel</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© Noble</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 14:32:28 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://deadchannel.xyz/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Everything Is a Variable</title>
      <link>https://deadchannel.xyz/posts/everything-is-a-variable/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 14:32:28 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://deadchannel.xyz/posts/everything-is-a-variable/</guid>
      <description>So I have been editting a clinical ethnography, which is to be peer-reviewed, and I had a sudden realization. My author fully wrote out the name of an organization for which she had already called defined the acronym earlier in the text. And that is when it hit me. Called! Defined! The acronym is merely a variable. And then I was looking at everything in the retail shop that work in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Computer</title>
      <link>https://deadchannel.xyz/posts/new-computer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 10:44:26 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://deadchannel.xyz/posts/new-computer/</guid>
      <description>This is me just trying to figure out how to clone into my GitHub and post from my laptop at work. Nothing to see here. These are not the droids you are looking for.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Mall</title>
      <link>https://deadchannel.xyz/posts/the-mall/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2022 14:16:54 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://deadchannel.xyz/posts/the-mall/</guid>
      <description>I had to go to the ear doctor today. I have fucked up ears, so I am a regular at my ENT clinic. The clinic is way off the beaten path, and I always have to walk through the parking lot of the Clackamas Town Center, between the lightrail and the clinic. It has become a normal thing for me to go to Barnes &amp;amp; Noble their to pick up the latest copy of the Atlantic with hopes of impressing the pretty girls answering the phones at the doctors office.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hugo and Git and Netlify Oh My</title>
      <link>https://deadchannel.xyz/posts/hugo-and-git-and-netlify-ohmy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 01:26:19 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://deadchannel.xyz/posts/hugo-and-git-and-netlify-ohmy/</guid>
      <description>Holy shit, this has been a test of fortitude. Every video, every post, every how-to, has been from a different operating system, different text editor/IDE, different versions of software (my first build was borked from install. It only took me two days to figure that oen out). Anyway, here it finally fucking is. My stupid self-important blog about god knows what. All I know, is that I need a proverbial toilet to spew my garbage, or else it becomes infectious and I get radioactive.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
