<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>deadchannel</title>
    <link>https://deadchannel.xyz/</link>
    <description>Recent content on deadchannel</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© Noble</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 01:08:41 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://deadchannel.xyz/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Mall</title>
      <link>https://deadchannel.xyz/posts/the-mall/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2022 14:16:54 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://deadchannel.xyz/posts/the-mall/</guid>
      <description>I had to go to the ear doctor today. I have fucked up ears, so I am a regular at my ENT clinic. The clinic is way off the beaten path, and I always have to walk through the parking lot of the Clackamas Town Center, between the lightrail and the clinic. It has become a normal thing for me to go to Barnes &amp;amp; Noble their to pick up the latest copy of the Atlantic with hopes of impressing the pretty girls answering the phones at the doctors office.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hugo and Git and Netlify Oh My</title>
      <link>https://deadchannel.xyz/posts/hugo-and-git-and-netlify-ohmy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 01:26:19 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://deadchannel.xyz/posts/hugo-and-git-and-netlify-ohmy/</guid>
      <description>Holy shit, this has been a test of fortitude. Every video, every post, every how-to, has been from a different operating system, different text editor/IDE, different versions of software (my first build was borked from install. It only took me two days to figure that oen out). Anyway, here it finally fucking is. My stupid self-important blog about god knows what. All I know, is that I need a proverbial toilet to spew my garbage, or else it becomes infectious and I get radioactive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://deadchannel.xyz/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 01:08:52 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://deadchannel.xyz/about/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The sky was the color of a television, tuned to a dead channel&amp;rdquo;
 William Gibson Neuromancer
  I am Noble. At least that what a handful of people still call me, at least when we&amp;rsquo;re in private. I had originally written a very pointed and telling bio for myself, in third person of course, that outlined my life, warts and all. But then I thought about it. If I really wanted to put myself out there, I would probably use my bith name.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
